I. M. Pei Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Correspondence, 1946-2016 (Box 1-135)
  - 1987 (Box 81)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 83)
    - University professorships (Box 83)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, New York, N.Y. (Box 83)
    - Yang, Shixuan (Box 83)
    - Zeckendorf, William (Box 83)
  - 1988 (Box 83)
    - Chen Cong-Zhou (Box 83)
    - Contributions (Box 83)
    - Édition Hazan (Box 83)
    - Fan mail (Box 83)
    - Fondation des Treilles, (1 folder) (Box 83, Box 84)
    - Harry Abrams Inc. (Box 84)
    - Interview requests (Box 84)
    - Magazines, (3 folders) (Box 84)
    - Newspapers (Box 84)
    - Publications (Box 84)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 84)
  - 1989 (Box 85)
    - "A" general (Box 85)
    - America-China Society (Box 85)
    - "B-C" general, (2 folders) (Box 85)
    - Chen Cong-Zhou (Box 85)
    - Contributions (Box 85)
    - "D-E" general (Box 85)
    - Édition Hazan (Box 85)
    - "F" general (Box 85)
    - Fukumaru, Mabo (Box 85)
    - "G" general (Box 85)
    - "H" general (Box 86)
    - Harry Abrams Inc., (4 folders) (Box 86)
    - "I-K" general (Box 86)
    - "L-S" general, (6 folders) (Box 87)
    - Speaking engagement requests, (2 folders) (Box 87)
    - "T-Z" general, (4 folders) (Box 88)
  - 1990 (Box 88)
    - American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters (Box 88)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 88)
    - "B-C" general (Box 88)
    - Claude Pompidou Foundation (Box 88)
    - Contributions (Box 88)
    - "D-H" general, (3 folders) (Box 88)
    - Harry Abrams Inc., (2 folders) (Box 88)
    - Interview requests (Box 89)
    - "J-O" general, (3 folders) (Box 89)
    - Magazines (Box 89)
    - Newspapers (Box 89)
    - "P" general (Box 89)
    - Publications (Box 89)
    - "R-Z" general, (6 folders) (Box 89)
  - 1991 (Box 89)
    - "A" general (Box 89)
    - American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters (Box 89)
    - American Institute of Architects, (2 folders) (Box 90)
    - Bunshaft, Gordon (Box 90)
    - "C-E" general (Box 90)
    - Chinese correspondence (Box 90)
    - Contributions (Box 90)
    - "G-J" general, (2 folders) (Box 90)
    - Interview requests (Box 90)
    - "K-N" general, (4 folders) (Box 90)
    - "O-S" general, (4 folders) (Box 91)
    - Smithsonian Institution (Box 91)
    - "T-Z" general, (4 folders) (Box 91)
  - 1992 (Box 91)
    - "A" general (Box 91)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box 91)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 91)
    - "B" general (Box 91)
    - Bei, Lin (Box 91)
    - "C" general (Box 92)
    - Chen Cong-Zhou (Box 92)
    - Chinese Cultural Center of Greater Toronto, Toronto, Canada (Box 92)
    - "D-H" general, (4 folders) (Box 92)
    - Harvard University Graduate School of Design, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 92)
    - "I" general (Box 92)
    - Interview requests (Box 92)
    - Invitations (Box 92)
    - "J" general (Box 92)
    - Jacobson, Leonard (Box 92)
    - "K-M" general, (3 folders) (Box 92)
    - Message logs (Box 93)
    - Montblanc de la Culture Award (Box 93)
    - "N-T" general, (5 folders) (Box 93)
    - Tien, Chang L. (Box 93)
    - "U-Z" general, (3 folders) (Box 93)
  - 1993 (Box 94)
    - "A" general (Box 94)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box 94)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 94)
    - American Society of the French Legion of Honor (Box 94)
    - "B-C" general, (2 folders) (Box 94)
    - Chen Cong-Zhou (Box 94)
    - Chinese correspondence (Box 94)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 94, Box 95)
    - "D-I" general, (3 folders) (Box 95)
    - Interview requests (Box 95)
    - "J-M" general, (3 folders) (Box 95)
    - Message logs, (1 folder) (Box 95, Box 96)
    - "N-P" general, (2 folders) (Box 96)
    - Pei Partnership Architects (Box 96)
    - "R-S" general, (3 folders) (Box 96)
    - Schedule (Box 96)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 96)
    - "T-Z" general, (2 folders) (Box 96)
  - 1994 (Box 97)
    - "A-B" general (Box 97)
    - America-China Society (Box 97)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box 97)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 97)
    - "C" general, (2 folders) (Box 97)
    - Chen Cong-Zhou (Box 97)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence, (2 folders); (7 folders) (Box 97, Box 98)
    - "D-F" general (Box 98)
    - "G-I" general, (2 folders) (Box 99)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 99)
    - Interview requests (Box 99)
    - "J-K" general (Box 99)
    - Korean-American Museum of Art and Cultural Center, Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 99)
    - "L-M" general, (2 folders) (Box 99)
    - Message logs, (2 folders) (Box 99)
    - Municipal Art Society (Box 100)
    - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, Mass. (Box 100)
    - "N-O" general, (2 folders) (Box 100)
    - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy (Box 100)
    - "P" general (Box 100)
    - Pei Partnership Architects (Box 100)
    - Prince of Wales Institute of Architecture, London, England (Box 100)
    - Pritzker Architecture Prize, 1991-1994 (Box 100)
    - Publications (Box 100)
    - "Q-R" general (Box 101)
    - Royal Academy of Arts (Box 101)
    - "S" General (Box 101)
    - Shanghai Jiao Tong University, Shanghai, China (Box 101)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 101)
    - "T-V" general, (2 folders) (Box 101)
    - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (Box 101)
    - Vienna Imperial Stables, Vienna, Austria (Box 101)
    - "W" general (Box 101)
    - White House Historical Association (Box 101)
    - Wiesner, Jerome (Box 101)
    - "X-Z" general (Box 102)
  - 1995 (Box 102)
    - "A" general (Box 102)
    - America-China Society (Box 102)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box 102)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 102)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 102)
      - General (Box 102)
      - New York chapter (Box 102)
    - Asia Society (Box 102)
    - "B" general (Box 102)
    - Beranek, Leo L. (Box 102)
    - Bezalel Academy, Jerusalem, Israel (Box 102)
    - "C" general (Box 102)
    - Chen Cong-Zhou (Box 102)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 102, Box 103)
    - "D-I" general, (2 folders) (Box 103)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 103)
    - Interview requests (Box 103)
    - "J-K" general (Box 103)
    - Korean-American Museum of Art and Cultural Center, Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 103)
    - "L" general (Box 103)
    - "M" general (Box 104)
    - Message logs, (3 folders) (Box 104)
    - "N-P" general, (2 folders) (Box 104)
    - Pei Cobb Freed & Partners (Box 104)
    - Pei Partnership Architects (Box 104)
    - "R-S" general, (2 folders) (Box 104)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 104)
    - "T-U" general (Box 105)
    - University Corporation of Atmospheric Research (Box 105)
    - "V-W" general (Box 105)
    - Walton, William (Box 105)
    - White House Historical Association (Box 105)
    - "Y-Z" general (Box 105)
  - 1996 (Box 105)
    - "A" general (Box 105)
    - America-China Society (Box 105)
    - American Institute of Architecture (Box 105)
      - General (Box 105)
      - New York chapter, (2 folders) (Box 105)
    - American Society of the French Legion of Honor (Box 105)
    - Asia Society (Box 105)
    - "B-C" general, (2 folders) (Box 106)
    - Chinese Cultural Center of America (Box 106)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence, (4 folders) (Box 106)
    - "D-I" general, (3 folders) (Box 107)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 107)
    - Immigration Coalition, New York, N.Y. (Box 107)
    - Interview requests (Box 107)
    - Invitations (Box 107)
    - "J-L" general, (2 folders) (Box 107)
    - Leonardo da Vinci's Horse sculpture (Box 107)
    - "M" general (Box 107)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 107)
    - Message logs, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 107, Box 108)
    - "N" general (Box 108)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 108)
    - "O-P" general, (2 folders) (Box 108)
    - Pei Cobb Freed & Partners (Box 108)
    - Pei Partnership Architects (Box 108)
    - "R-S" general, (2 folders) (Box 108)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 108)
    - "T" general (Box 109)
    - Tours (Box 109)
    - "U-Y" general, (2 folders) (Box 109)
    - Weymouth, Yann (Box 109)
    - Yang, Yingfeng (Yuyu) (Box 109)
  - 1997 (Box 109)
    - "A" general (Box 109)
    - America-China Society (Box 109)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 109)
    - "B-F" general, (2 folders) (Box 109)
    - Chen Cong-Zhou (Box 110)
    - Children of China Pediatrics Foundation (Box 110)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence, (4 folders) (Box 110)
    - Fan mail (Box 110)
    - "G-I" general (Box 110)
    - Interview requests (Box 110)
    - Invitations, (2 folders) (Box 110)
    - "J-M" general, (3 folders) (Box 111)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 111)
    - Message logs, (3 folders) (Box 111)
    - "N-P" general, (2 folders) (Box 111)
    - Pei Cobb Freed & Partners (Box 111)
    - Pei Partnership Architects (Box 111)
    - "R-S" general, (2 folders) (Box 111)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 111)
    - "T" general (Box 111)
    - "U-Z" general, (3 folders) (Box 112)
    - Zao, Wou-ki (Box 112)
  - 1998 (Box 112)
    - "A" general (Box 112)
    - America-China Society (Box 112)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 112)
    - "B-C" general, (2 folders) (Box 112)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence, (2 folders) (Box 112)
    - "D-G" general, (2 folders) (Box 113)
    - Fan mail (Box 113)
    - Fondation Claude Pompidou (Box 113)
    - "H-J" general (Box 113)
    - Interview requests, (2 folders) (Box 113)
    - Invitations, (3 folders) (Box 113)
    - "K-M" general (Box 113)
    - Message logs, (3 folders) (Box 114)
    - MUSE Film and Television (Box 114)
    - "N-R" general, (2 folders) (Box 114)
    - Pei Partnership Architects (Box 114)
    - Praemium Imperiale (Box 114)
    - "S" general (Box 114)
    - Society for the Preservation of New England Antiquities (Box 114)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 114)
    - St. John's University, Shanghai, China (Box 115)
    - "T-V" general (Box 115)
    - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation (Box 115)
    - "W-Z" general (Box 115)
  - 1999 (Box 115)
    - "A" general (Box 115)
    - America-China Society (Box 115)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box 115)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 115)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 115)
    - American Society of the French Legion of Honor (Box 115)
    - Asia Society (Box 115)
    - "B" general (Box 115)
    - Beijing, China, city planning (Box 115)
    - "C" general (Box 115)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence, (3 folders) (Box 116)
    - "D-F" general (Box 116)
    - Evans, Gareth (Box 116)
    - Fan mail, (3 folders) (Box 116)
    - "G-I" general (Box 116)
    - Interview requests (Box 116)
    - Invitations (Box 117)
    - "J-M" general, (2 folders) (Box 117)
    - Mellon, Paul (Box 117)
    - Message logs, (3 folders) (Box 117)
    - "N" general (Box 117)
    - National Council on the Arts (Box 117)
    - "O-P" general (Box 117)
    - Pei Cobb Freed & Partners (Box 117)
    - Pei Partnership Architects (Box 118)
    - "R-S" general, (2 folders) (Box 118)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 118)
    - St. John's University, Shanghai, China (Box 118)
    - "T-Z" general, (2 folders) (Box 118)
  - 2000 (Box 118)
    - "A" general (Box 118)
    - America-China Society (Box 118)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box 118)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 118)
    - American Institute of Architecture (Box 118)
      - General (Box 118)
      - New York chapter (Box 118)
    - American Society of the French Legion of Honor (Box 118)
    - Asia Society (Box 118)
    - "B-D" general, (2 folders) (Box 119)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence, (2 folders) (Box 119)
    - "E-F" general (Box 119)
    - Fan mail (Box 119)
    - "G-H" general (Box 119)
    - Interview requests (Box 119)
    - Invitations, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 119, Box 120)
    - "J-M" general, (2 folders) (Box 120)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 120)
    - Message logs, (2 folders) (Box 120)
    - "N-P" general, (2 folders) (Box 120)
    - Pei Cobb Freed & Partners (Box 120)
    - Pei Partnership Architects (Box 120)
    - "R-S" general, (2 folders) (Box 120)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 120)
    - "T-Z" general (Box 121)
    - Teatro Architettura Museo, Torino, Italy (Box 121)
  - 2001 (Box 121)
    - "A" general (Box 121)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box 121)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 121)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 121)
      - General (Box 121)
      - New York chapter (Box 121)
    - Artists (Box 121)
    - Asia Society (Box 121)
    - "B-C" general, (2 folders) (Box 121)
    - Chen Cong-Zhou (Box 121)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence, (1 folder) (Box 121, Box 122)
    - "D-F" general (Box 122)
    - Fan mail (Box 122)
    - Feng shui (Box 122)
    - "G-I" general (Box 122)
    - Interview requests (Box 122)
    - Invitations (Box 122)
    - "J-N" general, (3 folders) (Box 122)
    - Message logs, (1 folder) (Box 122, Box 123)
    - "O-P" general, (2 folders) (Box 123)
    - Pei Partnership Architects (Box 123)
    - "R-S" general, (2 folders) (Box 123)
    - Smithsonian Institution (Box 123)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 123)
    - Teatro Architettura Museo, Torino, Italy (Box 123)
    - "T-Z" general, (2 folders) (Box 123)
  - 2002 (Box 123)
    - "A" general (Box 123)
    - American Academy of Achievement (Box 123)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box 124)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 124)
    - "B" general (Box 124)
    - Brown, J. Carter (Box 124)
    - "C-D" general (Box 124)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence (Box 124)
    - "E-I" general (Box 124)
    - Interview requests (Box 124)
    - Invitations (Box 124)
    - "J-M" general, (2 folders) (Box 124)
    - Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group (Box 124)
    - Message logs, (3 folders) (Box 125)
    - "N-S" general, (3 folders) (Box 125)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 125)
    - "T-Z" general, (2 folders) (Box 125)
  - 2003 (Box 125)
    - "A" general (Box 125)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box 125)
    - Asia Society (Box 126)
    - "B-C" general, (2 folders) (Box 126)
    - Chen Cong-Zhou (Box 126)
    - Chillida, Eduardo (Box 126)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence (Box 126)
    - "D-F" general (Box 126)
    - Fan mail (Box 126)
    - "H-I" general (Box 126)
    - Interview requests (Box 126)
    - Invitations (Box 126)
    - "J-L" general (Box 126)
    - Leonard, Eason (Box 126)
    - "M" general (Box 126)
    - Message logs, (1 folder) (Box 126, Box 127)
    - "N-S" general, (2 folders) (Box 127)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 127)
    - "T-Z" general (Box 127)
  - 2004 (Box 127)
    - "A" general (Box 127)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box 127)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 127)
      - General (Box 127)
      - New York chapter (Box 127)
    - Asia Society (Box 127)
    - "B-F" general (Box 127)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence (Box 127)
    - Fan mail (Box 127)
    - "G-H" general (Box 128)
    - Interview requests (Box 128)
    - Invitations (Box 128)
    - "J-L" general (Box 128)
    - Leonard, Eason (Box 128)
    - "M" general (Box 128)
    - Message logs, (2 folders) (Box 128)
    - "N-P" general (Box 128)
    - Pei Partnership Architects (Box 128)
    - "R-S" general (Box 128)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 129)
    - "T-Z" general (Box 129)
  - 2005 (Box 129)
    - "A-F" general, (3 folders) (Box 129)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence (Box 129)
    - Fan mail (Box 129)
    - Freed, James (Box 129)
    - "G-I" general (Box 129)
    - Interview requests (Box 129)
    - Invitations (Box 129)
    - "J-P" general, (2 folders) (Box 129)
    - Message logs, (2 folders) (Box 130)
    - "R-S" general, (2 folders) (Box 130)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 130)
    - "T-Z" general (Box 130)
  - 2006 (Box 130)
    - "A-I" general, (2 folders) (Box 130)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence (Box 130)
    - Interview requests (Box 130)
    - Invitations (Box 130)
    - "J-M" general (Box 130)
    - Message logs, (2 folders) (Box 131)
    - "N-S" general (Box 131)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 131)
    - "T-Z" general (Box 131)
  - 2007 (Box 131)
    - "A-F" general (Box 131)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence (Box 131)
    - Fan mail (Box 131)
    - "G-N" general (Box 131)
    - Invitations (Box 131)
    - Message logs, (2 folders) (Box 132)
    - "P-S" general (Box 132)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 132)
    - "T-Y" general (Box 132)
  - 2008 (Box 132)
    - "A-F" general (Box 132)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence (Box 132)
    - Fan mail (Box 132)
    - "G-M" general (Box 132)
    - Invitations (Box 132)
    - Message logs, (1 folder) (Box 132, Box 133)
    - "N-R" general (Box 133)
    - "S-Z" general (Box 133)
    - Speaking engagement requests (Box 133)
  - 2009 (Box 133)
    - "A-F" general (Box 133)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence (Box 133)
    - Fan mail (Box 133)
    - "G-L" general (Box 133)
    - Invitations (Box 133)
    - "M-N" general (Box 133)
    - Message logs, (2 folders) (Box 134)
    - "P-Y" general, (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - 2010 (Box 134)
    - "A-C" general (Box 134)
    - Chinese correspondence (Box 134)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence (Box 134)
    - "D-L" general (Box 134)
    - Fan mail (Box 134)
    - Invitations (Box 134)
    - "M-Z" general (Box 134)
    - Message logs, (2 folders) (Box 135)
  - 2011 (Box 135)
    - "A-F" general (Box 135)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence (Box 135)
    - Fan mail (Box 135)
    - "G-O" general (Box 135)
    - Invitations (Box 135)
    - "P-Z" general (Box 135)
  - 2012 (Box 135)
    - "A-F" general (Box 135)
    - Copies of outgoing correspondence (Box 135)
    - Fan mail (Box 135)
    - "G-Z" general (Box 135)
    - Invitations (Box 135)
  - 2013, "A-Z" general (Box 135)
  - 2014, "A-Z" general (Box 135)
  - 2015, "A-Z" general (Box 135)
  - 2016, "A-Z" general (Box 135)
- Projects Completed/Inactive, 1959-2013 (Box 136-377)
  Correspondence, meeting minutes, proposals, contracts, financial documents, memoranda, clippings, studies, reports, blueprints, architectural renderings, plans, drawings, maps, and photographs relating to projects for which Pei was the design principal. The designation "completed/inactive" was used by Pei's staff and has been retained. The files primarily track project history from the proposal stage to project completion, and in some cases provide details related to projects long after they have become inactive.
  Arranged alphabetically by city and alphabetically therein by building or project name and subject.
  - Andover, Mass., Phillips Academy Memorial, 1965-1966 (Box 136)
  - Annapolis, Md., St. John's College, 1961-1965 See also Container OV 14, Annapolis (Box 136)
  - Arlington, Va., Robert F. Kennedy grave site, Arlington National Cemetery, 1968-1972 (Box 136)
  - Armonk, N.Y., International Business Machines Corp., entrance pavilion and site enhancement, 1983-1985 (Box 136)
  - Asheville, N.C., Akzona Corporate Headquarters, 1979-1982 (Box 136)
  - Atlanta, Ga. (Box 136)
    - Albritton Development Co., 1985-1987 (Box 136)
    - Gulf Oil Building, 2008 (Box 136)
    - Ritz-Carlton Hotel site, 1987 (Box 136)
    - Wildwood Office Park, 1989-1991, 2003 (Box 136)
  - Baltimore, Md., World Trade Center, 2006 (Box 136)
  - Barcelona, Spain (Box 136)
    - La Caixa Bank Headquarters (Box 136)
      - 1991-1992 See also Container OV 17, Presentation drawings, (2 folders) (Box 136)
      - 1993, (1 folder) (Box 136, Box 137)
      - 1994-2002 See also Containers OV 17-18, Blueprints (Box 137)
    - International Trade Center, 1990 (Box 137)
  - Beijing, China (Box 137)
    - Bank of China Head Office See also Container OV 1, Beijing (Box 137)
      - General (Box 137)
        - 1994-1999, (6 folders) (Box 137)
        - 2000-2001 (Box 138)
      - Topical files, 1995-2003, (3 folders) (Box 138)
    - Fragrant Hill Hotel (Box 138)
      - General (Box 138)
        - 1978-1979, Aug., (3 folders) (Box 138)
        - 1979, Sept.-2004, (8 folders) (Box 139)
      - Gift brochure, 1981-1983, (2 folders) (Box 139)
      - Opening, 1982 (Box 140)
      - Topical files, 1982-1983 (Box 140)
  - Berlin, Germany, Deutsches Historisches Museum (Box 140)
    - Background information, circa 1996, (2 folders) (Box 140)
    - Correspondence (Box 140)
      - 1995-1997, (3 folders) (Box 140)
      - 1998-2000, (7 folders) (Box 141)
      - 2001-2012, (4 folders) (Box 142)
    - Photographs, 2004-2005, (2 folders) (Box 142)
    - Topical files, 1997-2003 See also Container OV 2, Berlin (Box 142)
  - Bethlehem, N.Y., General Electric Co. Chemical and Metallurgical Division report, 1967 (Box 143)
  - Beverly Hills, Calif., Creative Artists Agency headquarters, 1986-1996, 2007 (Box 143)
  - Birmingham, Ala., Kirklin Clinic, 1988-1997, 2004 (Box 143)
  - Bloomington, Ind., Indiana University Art Museum and Academic Building (Box 143)
    - 1972-1984, (2 folders) (Box 143)
    - 1993-2007 (Box 143)
  - Boston, Mass. (Box 143)
    - Christian Science Center, 1991, 2001-2006 (Box 143)
    - Downtown North General Neighborhood Renewal Plan, 1961, (1 folder) (Box 143, Box 144)
    - Government Center Urban Renewal Plan (Box 144)
      - Binders, 1961, (4 folders) (Box 144)
      - General, 1960-1964, (2 folders) (Box 144)
    - John F. Kennedy Library (Box 145)
      - Binders, 1963-1976, (6 folders); (5 folders) (Box 145, Box 146)
      - General (Box 146)
        - 1965-1970, (2 folders) (Box 146)
        - 1971, (2 folders) (Box 147)
        - 1972 See also Container OV 18, Boston, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 147, Box 148)
        - 1973, (5 folders) (Box 148)
        - 1974, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 148, Box 149)
        - 1975-1978, (5 folders) (Box 149)
        - 1979-2010, (3 folders) (Box 150)
      - Topical files, 1973-1979 (Box 150)
    - John Hancock Tower, 1968-1971 (Box 150)
    - Museum of Fine Arts West Wing (Box 150)
      - General (Box 150)
        - 1977-2002, 2011, (5 folders) (Box 150)
      - Topical files, 1977-1981 (Box 151)
  - Boulder, Colo., National Center for Atmospheric Research (Box 151)
    - Binder, 1997 (Box 151)
    - General, 1985-2010, (2 folders) (Box 151)
    - Topical files, 1967-1972 (Box 151)
    - Twenty-fifth anniversary, 1985-1986 (Box 151)
  - Brooklyn, N.Y., Bedford-Stuyvesant Superblock (Box 151)
    - Binders, 1967, (3 folders) (Box 151)
    - General See also Container OV 2, Brooklyn (Box 151)
      - 1967-1974, (2 folders) (Box 151)
      - 1992 (Box 152)
  - Cambridge, Mass. (Box 152)
    - Cecil and Ida Green Center for Earth Sciences, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1964, 1996 (Box 152)
    - Gateway to Guilford Northpoint, 1999-2003 See also Container OV 2, Cambridge, (2 folders) (Box 152)
    - Ralph Landau Chemical Engineering Building, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1972-1977, (2 folders) (Box 152)
    - Weisner Building/Center for Arts and Media Technology, Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 152)
      - Building dedication, 1985 (Box 152)
      - General (Box 152)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 152)
        - 1980, (1 folder) (Box 152, Box 153)
        - 1981-1987, 1995-2010 See also Digital Files, mss82878_123_017, (6 folders) (Box 153)
  - Chicago, Ill., University Gardens Apartments, Hyde Park, circa 1959-1962, 2005-2006 See also Container OV 3, Chicago (Box 153)
  - Cleveland, Ohio (Box 153)